The write-ups for SNHUPEDIA

CETA IDE:

	Manchester New Hampshire January 13, 2020 was the day the CETA IDE building was complete. SNHU first started working
	 on this building back in 2018. SNHU’s College of Engineering, Technology and Aeronautics was established in 2017 after
	 the sudden closure of Daniel Webster College.

https://www.snhu.edu/about-us/newsroom/press-releases/snhu-opens-ceta-facility
Lauren Keane Jan 14, 2020, et al. “SNHU Opens New College of Engineering, Technology and Aeronautics Facility.” Southern New Hampshire University, https://www.snhu.edu/about-us/newsroom/press-releases/snhu-opens-ceta-facility.


Penman Stadium:

	Mark A. Ouellette Stadium opened in early 2018. The new complex houses a 1,500-seat stadium overlooking a Field Turf
	surface that includes Mosco lighting. The field is lined for soccer, women's and men's lacrosse, and field hockey.
	A sound system, as well as a state-of-the-art video and scoreboard from Daktronics, adorns the new stadium.

https://snhupenmen.com/facilities/penmen-stadium/1
“Southern New Hampshire University .” Southern New Hampshire University, https://snhupenmen.com/facilities/penmen-stadium/1.


 SNHU Shapiro Library:

	The Shapiro Library empowers the SNHU community by guiding them through the complex information landscape and connects
	them with the resources needed to be successful. Whether you’re online or on campus,  supports SNHU students of all kinds.
	Using innovative services and technologies, the library delivers information and instruction necessary for academic success
	and lifelong learning. For students using the main campus, Shapiro Library moved into the Library Learning Commons building on
	September 2, 2014. In addition to library services, the Library Learning Commons also includes an IT help desk, the Wolak
	Learning Center, the Zachos Commons Café and the. This 50,000 square foot, $18 million building is located at the center
	of campus and provides a beautiful, state-of-the-art facility for students to conduct their academic work.

https://www.snhu.edu/student-experience/campus-experience/shapiro-library
“Shapiro Library.” Southern New Hampshire University, https://www.snhu.edu/student-experience/campus-experience/shapiro-library.


Robert Frost:

	Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipiscing elit, urna consequat felis vehicula class ultricies mollis dictumst,
	aenean non a in donec nulla. Phasellus ante pellentesque erat cum risus consequat imperdiet aliquam, integer placerat et turpis
	mi eros nec lobortis taciti, vehicula nisl litora tellus ligula porttitor metus.  Vivamus integer non suscipit taciti mus etiam at
	primis tempor sagittis sit, euismod libero facilisi aptent elementum felis blandit cursus gravida sociis erat ante, eleifend lectus nullam dapibus netus feugiat curae
	curabitur est ad. Massa curae fringilla porttitor quam sollicitudin iaculis aptent leo
	ligula euismod dictumst, orci penatibus mauris eros etiam praesent erat volutpat posuere hac.
	Metus fringilla nec ullamcorper odio aliquam lacinia conubia mauris tempor, etiam ultricies proin quisque lectus sociis id
	tristique, integer phasellus taciti pretium adipiscing tortor sagittis ligula.
